Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Twin Fates=
=مصيران توأمان=
=Episode 20= (The Return of Consciousness)
=الحلقة 20= (عودة الوعي)
Who is this?
من هذا؟
I never I'd find a body
لن أجد جثة أبدًا
in this secret chamber.
في هذه الغرفة السرية.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
He's Lord Scarlet Flame, Yanlie.
إنه اللورد القرمزي اللهب، يانلي.
After his death, Bai Li removed his primordial soul
بعد وفاته، أزال باي لي روحه البدائية
before putting it into your body.
قبل إدخاله إلى جسمك.
My body?
جسدي؟
Mm.
مم.
How could that be?
كيف يمكن أن يكون ذلك؟
I'll tell you everything
سأخبرك بكل شيء
in detail after this.
بالتفصيل بعد هذا.
Please keep your words
من فضلك حافظ على كلماتك
and remove the golden phoenix feather out of this body.
وأخرج ريشة الفينيق الذهبية من هذا الجسم.
Golden phoenix...
طائر الفينيق الذهبي...
Golden feather...
ريشة ذهبية...
There's a divine beast's primordial soul in your body.
هناك روح الوحش الإلهي البدائية في جسدك.
And this golden feather only resonates with you.
وهذه الريشة الذهبية تتردد صداها معك فقط.
You're still alive?
هل مازلت على قيد الحياة؟
Li Cang, you're outrageous!
لي كانج، أنت فظيع!
(No way,)
(مستحيل،)
(this black miasma is just like what Chi Yu had then.)
(هذا المخاط الأسود يشبه تمامًا ما كان لدى تشي يو في ذلك الوقت.)
(Could it be...)
(هل يمكن أن يكون...)
He's not Li Cang.
إنه ليس لي كانغ.
I thought of making you the ruler of Hong.
لقد فكرت في جعلك حاكما لهونغ.
To my surprise, you've been useless.
لمفاجأتي، كنت عديم الفائدة.
Since that's the case,
وبما أن هذه هي الحالة،
someone else should take the throne.
يجب أن يأخذ شخص آخر العرش.
You're here for me, aren't you?
أنت هنا من أجلي، أليس كذلك؟
Surrender the golden phoenix feather
استسلم ريشة الفينيق الذهبية
and I'll go with you.
وسأذهب معك.
Hmph.
همف.
I will take
سوف آخذ
both of your lives!
كلا حياتكما!
Chi Yu, now!
تشي يو، الآن!
The Silver Fox Clan has tried to sow discord between Chi Yu and Ji Yuchen
حاولت عشيرة الثعلب الفضي إثارة الخلاف بين تشي يو وجي يوتشن
in order to take advantage of it and seize the golden feather,
من أجل الاستفادة منه والاستيلاء على الريشة الذهبية،
giving birth to a disaster in the mortal realm.
ولادة كارثة في عالم البشر.
I must stop them.
يجب أن أوقفهم.
Please come up with a reading when it is time.
يرجى تقديم القراءة عندما يحين الوقت.
And pass this token to Chi Yu.
وأعطي هذه الرمز إلى تشي يو.
He remembers what my blood smells like.
يتذكر رائحة دمي.
Chi Yu, quick!
تشي يو، سريعًا!
Get the golden phoenix feather!
احصل على ريشة الفينيق الذهبية!
Chi Yu, you've regained your consciousness.
تشي يو، لقد استعدت وعيك.
Don't you marry him.
لا تتزوجيه
You're mine.
أنت لي.
Well,
حسنًا،
I was rude to you then.
لقد كنت وقحا معك حينها.
I really had no idea what I was doing.
لم يكن لدي أي فكرة عما كنت أفعله.
I understand.
أفهم.
You weren't yourself,
لم تكن نفسك
and you didn't mean to hurt me.
ولم تقصد أن تؤذيني.
There are two souls in you.
هناك روحان في داخلك.
We finally know the truth.
وأخيرًا عرفنا الحقيقة.
As for
أما بالنسبة ل
the wedding...
حفل الزفاف...
Of course it's not valid.
بالطبع هذا غير صحيح.
What will you do
ماذا ستفعل؟
after this?
بعد هذا؟
Now that I've regained my consciousness
الآن بعد أن استعدت وعيي
and the contract has come into effect,
وقد دخل العقد حيز التنفيذ،
it's time to settle both old and new scores
لقد حان الوقت لتسوية الحسابات القديمة والجديدة
with the Silver Fox Clan.
مع عشيرة الثعلب الفضي.
I'll wait for your return.
سأنتظر عودتك.
Where is Yanlie's golden phoenix feather?
أين ريشة طائر الفينيق الذهبي ليانلي؟
The contract between Mu Lingxue and Chi Yu
العقد بين Mu Lingxue و Chi Yu
is way too powerful.
إنها قوية جدًا.
I couldn't withstand it,
لم أستطع أن أتحمل ذلك،
and they managed to seize Yanlie's golden phoenix feather.
وتمكنوا من الاستيلاء على ريشة الفينيق الذهبية الخاصة بـ يانلي.
Now Chi Yu's consciousness and powers have been restored.
الآن تم استعادة وعي تشي يو وقواه .
The Soul-Pulling Spell on Yanlie
تعويذة سحب الروح على يانلي
is gone too.
لقد رحل أيضاً.
You good-for-nothing!
أنت لا تصلح لشيء!
My carefully crafted plan has gone down the drain because of you!
لقد ذهبت خطتي التي صممتها بعناية أدراج الرياح بسببك!
Have you lost your mind?
هل فقدت عقلك؟
How dare you betray me!
كيف تجرؤ على خيانتي!
You think a mere tiny dagger
هل تعتقد أن مجرد خنجر صغير
can kill me?
هل يستطيع أن يقتلني؟
I'll give you an ugly death.
سأعطيك موتة قبيحة.
Ah!
اه!
Go to hell
اذهب إلى الجحيم
and be a ruler as you please.
وكن حاكما كما تشاء.
How can this...
كيف يمكن لهذا...
Master.
يتقن.
Take a good look at it.
أنظر إليه جيدا.
This is Windcutter, the dagger you gave me.
هذا هو Windcutter، الخنجر الذي أعطيته لي.
It's used to slay divine and demonic beasts.
يتم استخدامه لقتل الوحوش الإلهية والشيطانية.
(Well done.)
(أحسنت.)
Master.
يتقن.
I'll get you the Xuanzhu Jade as soon as possible.
سأحضر لك اليشم Xuanzhu في أقرب وقت ممكن.
For the sake of power and glory,
من أجل القوة والمجد،
I'll make it happen at all costs.
سأجعل ذلك يحدث بأي ثمن.
Bai Li, show yourself!
باي لي، أظهر نفسك!
Bai Li's primordial spirit has escaped again, hasn't it?
لقد هربت روح باي لي البدائية مرة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
No. Her consciousness and spirit are both destroyed.
لا، لقد تم تدمير وعيها وروحها .
An Sha killed her.
قتلها أن شا.
(It's all over now.)
(لقد انتهى كل شيء الآن.)
Let's go home.
دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل.
(Grand Tutor Mu Heng)
(المعلم الكبير مو هنغ)
(had always been a diligent and dedicated subject.)
(كان دائمًا موضوعًا مجتهدًا ومخلصًا.)
(Unfortunately,)
(للأسف،)
(he was framed by traitor Li Cang.)
(تم الإيقاع به من قبل الخائن لي كانج.)
(My negligence)
(إهمالي)
(has wronged such a loyal subject,)
(لقد ظلم مثل هذا الموضوع المخلص)
(leading to this tragedy.)
(مما أدى إلى هذه المأساة.)
(I)
(أنا)
(Memorial Tablet of Late Father, Mu Heng) (feel deeply regret.)
(لوحة تذكارية للأب الراحل، مو هينج) (أشعر بالأسف العميق.)
(With this edict of self-blame,)
(مع هذا المرسوم من اللوم الذاتي)
(I'd like)
(أود أن)
(to clear Grand Tutor's family's name and restore their innocence.)
(لتطهير اسم عائلة المعلم الأكبر واستعادة براءتهم.)
(Grand Tutor Mu Heng)
(المعلم الكبير مو هنغ)
(deserves to be part of the ancestral temple,)
(يستحق أن يكون جزءًا من المعبد الأجدادي)
(and he shall be conferred the title of Duke Mu)
(وسيُمنح لقب دوق مو)
(to display my repentance)
(لإظهار توبتي)
(and my utmost respect for his achievements.)
(واحترامي الشديد لإنجازاته).
(Father.)
(أب.)
(Mother.)
(الأم.)
(At last, I've cleared your name.)
(أخيرًا، لقد قمت بتطهير اسمك.)
(Memorial Tablet of Late Father, Mu Heng)
(لوحة تذكارية للأب الراحل، مو هينج)
(Once I've completed the sacrifice)
(بعد أن أكملت التضحية)
(for you on the Day of Xihe,)
(لك في يوم Xihe)
(you shall always be under this sunlight)
(سوف تكون دائمًا تحت ضوء الشمس هذا)
(and live as freely as you do now.)
(وعيش بحرية كما تفعل الآن.)
=Twin Fates= =End of Episode 20=
=مصيران توأمان= =نهاية الحلقة 20=
♪In a world of sorrows, every encounter is fleeting♪
♪في عالم من الأحزان، كل لقاء عابر♪
♪Life is short but slumber is long on Penglai Island♪
♪الحياة قصيرة ولكن النوم طويل في جزيرة بنغلاي♪
♪In dreams, mountains and flowers are as beautiful as jade♪
♪في الأحلام، الجبال والزهور جميلة مثل اليشم♪
♪All I ever wish for is an old friend's return♪
♪كل ما أتمناه هو عودة صديق قديم♪
♪Majestic as a soaring dragon, veiling the sun with drifting clouds♪
♪مهيب مثل التنين المرتفع، يحجب الشمس بالغيوم المنجرفة♪
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
♪On the Ximo River, who was left behind?♪
♪على نهر شيمو، من بقي خلفه؟♪
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
♪طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سرًا♪
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
♪لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل♪
♪Leaving only two lonely lines♪
♪ترك خطين وحيدين فقط♪
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
♪حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع♪
♪Pair after pair, swallows draw my envious gaze♪
♪زوجًا بعد زوج، تجذب السنونو نظرتي الحسود♪
♪Scene after scene, in dreams I cannot reach♪
♪مشهد بعد مشهد، في الأحلام لا أستطيع الوصول إليه♪
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪